Well, if we learned
one thing today, Cheese,
it's that cheerleaders
and high explosives don't mix.
Cheese:
You can say that again, Mac.
Well, I couldn't have done it
without you, buddy.
You're a genius.
Oh, yeah? Well, then how come
I can't get my VCR
to stop blinking 12:00?
( laughter )
So, what'd you guys think?
( phone rings )
I got it, I got it!
The phone, the phone!
Hello.
Hold on, please--
Joey, it's your mom.
It's your mommy.
Oh, that's nice.
Ma, so what did you think?
Well
that was, um
okay.
It wasn't the best.
That was one of
the worst things ever.
And not just on TV.
What are we going
to tell him?
Well, the-the
lighting was okay.
Oh, no, you don't--
you got lighting last time.
Lighting is mine.
I have costumes.
Oh, great.
That means I'm stuck with
"So, we were watching
you in there
and you were sitting
right here. Whoa."
What are you
going to do, Pheebs?
I don't know, I don't know.
I can't lie to him again.
Oh, no, I'm--
No, I'm just going to press my
breasts up against him.
And say nothing?
Uh-huh. Yeah, that's right.
All right, bye.
Wow, well, my folks
really liked it.
So, what did you guys think?
Well, it wasn't that good.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Phoebe, do you think
that your favorite animal
says very much about you?
What, you mean
behind my back?
Oh! You guys, oh, my God,
you're never going to believe
what happened
to me today.
I am sitting in my office...
You guys, you guys,
you're not going
to believe what
my agent just told me.
Joey, in the middle
of a story, here.
Oh, sorry, sorry, you finish.
Okay, so anyway,
I'm sitting in my office
and guess who walks in?
I'm going to be
on two TV shows!
Oh, that's great!
Really?
Joey.
You weren't finished?
Yeah
"Guess who walks into my office"
is the end of my story.
It was Ralph Lauren.
Ralph Lauren
walked into my office.
Uh, Rach.
If you're going to start
another story, at least
let me finish mine.
It's the same story.
Well, it's really long.
Oh, my God.
Anyway, Ralph just came in
to tell me that he's
so happy with my work
that he wants me to be
the new merchandising
manager for Polo retail.
Ooh.
Still get a discount
on wedding dresses?
Yeah.
I'm so happy for you!
I'm so glad.
Well, these really are
"the days of our lives."
What?
Well, since you ask...
they want me back on
Days of our Lives.
Oh, my God.
I get... I get
a big pay raise!
Oh, great!
I'll be playing Drake Ramoray's
twin brother, Stryker.
Oooh.
I get to hire my own assistant.
( squeals )
Well...
I got a head rush
from standing up too fast.
And you were at this job
for four years?
That's right.
Okay.
Well, this is all
very impressive, Hilda.
Um, I just have
one last question for you.
How did I do?
Was this okay?
What?
I've never
interviewed anyone before.
I've actually never had anyone
work for me before.
Although when I was a kid
we did have a maid
but this isn't the same thing.
No, dear. It's not.
No. Yeah.
And I know that.
All right, well,
thank you so much for coming in.
It was nice to meet you.
Good meeting you.
All right.
I'm a total pro.
Hello?
Wow.
Um.
Hi, yes, I'm sorry
the models are actually
down the hall.
Actually, I'm here
about the assistant job.
Really?
Okay. Well, then...
All right
well, just have
a seat there.
Um, so, what's...
what is...
what's your name?
Tag Jones.
Uh-huh. Go on.
That's it.
That's my whole name.
That's your whole name.
Okay, of course it is.
Okay, well, let's just
have a look-see here.
I know I haven't worked
in an office before
and I really don't have
a lot of experience.
Oh, come on, now,
what are you talking about?
You've got three years
painting houses.
Two whole summers
at T.G.I. Friday's.
It's lame, I know.
But I'm a goal-oriented person,
very eager to learn.
Okay, just hold on
a second, please.
Sorry, it's for Human Resources.
Everybody has to do it.
Would you just stand up, please?
No, no, no, no, no.
Hey.
Ch-ch-ch-ch!
Anyway, I should go.
Okay. Bye.
Hey, sweetie.
Hi, sweetie.
So what was with
all the whispering?
I can't tell you.
It's a secret.
Secret?
Married people aren't
supposed to have secrets
between one another.
We have too much love
and respect for one another.
Aww.
But still, no.
No, I'm serious.
We should tell
each other everything.
I do not have any
secrets from you.
Really?
Okay, so why don't you tell me
what happened to Ross
junior year at Disneyland?
Oh, no, no. I can't do that.
If you tell me
I'll tell you
what Phoebe said.
Okay.
So, Ross and I are
going to Disneyland
and we stop at this
restaurant for tacos.
And when I say restaurant,
I mean a guy, a hibachi
and the trunk of his car.
So Ross has about ten tacos
and anyway, we're on
Space Mountain
and Ross starts to feel
a little... iffy.
Oh, my God,
he threw up?
No, he visited a town
a little south of throw up.
( laughing )
So, what was Phoebe's secret?
Nancy Thompson, from
Phoebe's old massage place
is getting fired.
Oh.
That's it?
I gave up my
Disneyland story for that?
That's right.
You lose, sucker.
Please still marry me.
Chandler, you have
an assistant, right?
Did she call?
You-you told her
I was sick, right?
Always tell her I am sick.
No, I just don't know...
how do you decide who to hire?
I mean, I've got it
narrowed down to two people
One of them has great references
and a lot of experience
and then there's this guy...
What about him?
I love him.
He's so pretty
I want to cry.
I don't know what to do.
Tell me what to do.
Come on,
you know what to do.
You hire the first one.
You don't hire an assistant
because they're cute
you hire them
because they're qualified.
Uh-huh.
No, I hear what you're saying,
and that makes a lot of sense
but can I just
say one more thing?
Look how pretty.
Let me see.
Oh, my God.
Oh...
But no.
No, you can't hire him
'cause it's not professional.
Um, this is for me, yes?
Okay, you're right.
I'll hire Hilda tomorrow.
Dumb old
perfect-for-the-job Hilda.
Let me see this guy.
Wow.
Don't show this to Monica.
And don't tell her
about the "wow."
( knocking )
Hey, Joey.
Hey, Terry.
Nice to see you again.
It's been awhile, huh?
Boy, it's funny.
These halls look smaller
than they used to.
It's a different building.
So...
Stryker Ramoray, huh?
When do you want me to start?
Why don't we
start right now?
Okay.
Here are the audition scenes.
Audition?
I thought you were going
to offer me the part.
Why would you think that?
Well, I was Dr. Drake Ramoray,
Stryker's twin brother.
Who looks more like me
than me, right?
Everybody has to audition.
You know, Terry
I don't really need to do this.
I got my own cable TV series.
With a robot.
I'm sorry, Joey,
that's the way it is.
Well...
I guess you think
you're pretty special, huh?
Sitting up here in your
fancy small-hall building.
Making stars jump through
hoops for you, huh?
Well, you know what?
This is one star whose hoop...
this is a star that the hoop...
this hoop
I was
Dr. Drake Ramoray!
Hi, Tag.
What are you doing here?
I just wanted to come by
and thank you for not laughing
in my face yesterday.
And I noticed there aren't
any plants in your office
so I wanted
to bring you your first.
There is a plant
in your office.
Kinda.
Right.
So, I guess I shouldn't put
"good at noticing stuff"
on my resume.
Thank you.
Anyway, I'm guessing
you hired somebody.
Well...
Gotcha.
Thanks again
for meeting with me.
But I hired you.
What?
Yeah, you got the job.
You're my new assistant.
I am?
Yeah.
I can't believe it.
Me either.
Um...
All right, first thing
I need you to do
is go downstairs and
find a woman named Hilda
and tell her to go home.
Hey.
Hey, good. You're home.
Oh, that's always nicer
to hear than
"Aw, crap, you again."
Hey, sweetie. Mmm...
Hey.
I made you
a surprise.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah. Tacos!
Ever since you told me
that story
I've had such a
craving for them.
Did you not understand
the story?
Hey.
Ross!
Hey, what's up?
Nothing much.
Just trying to figure out
what I'm going to do for dinner.
Huh.
You know?
Hey, whoo,
what's...
What's that, uh, dinner stuff?
Y-you making dinner?
( timer dings )
No. Shh!
What you got over there, tacos?
No. No.
They, um...
they're just, uh...
They're... they're
ground beef smilies.
Uh... those are tacos.
Excuse me, Mr. Mexico!
Uh, either way, I'll pass.
Still can't eat those.
( wry chuckle )
( Monica stifling laughter )
( laughing )
What's so funny?
I'm not laughing.
You told her!
Nancy Thompson's getting fired.
Okay, okay.
I had food poisoning.
It's not like
I chose to do it.
It's not like...
it's not like
I said, "Oh, what would
make this ride more fun?"
You're right. You're right.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't be laughing.
I should be
laying down papers for you.
( stifling laughter )
( laughing derisively )
How could you tell her?
I had to, okay?
We're getting married.
Married couples can't keep
secrets from one another.
Oh, really? Well, I...
I guess Monica should know
about Atlantic City.
Du-ude!
What happened
in Atlantic City?
Well, Chandler and I
were in a bar...
Did you not hear me say,
"Du-ude!"?
And this girl is making
eyes at Chandler. Okay?
So, after a while, he...
he goes over to her
and, uh... after a minute
or two, I see them kissing.
Now, I know what
you're thinking.
Chandler's not type of guy
who just goes to bars
and makes out with girls.
And you're right, Chandler's
not the type of guy
who just goes to bars
and makes out with girls.
You kissed a guy?! Oh!
Oh, my God!
In my defense, it was dark,
and he was a very pretty guy.
( laughing harder )
Oh, Mon,
I laughed so hard.
Ho-ho! So hard we had to throw
out your underwear again?
Whatever, dude,
you kissed a guy.
Hi.
Hey.
Ooh, how's Hilda?
She working out?
Oh, my new assistant is...
working out, yes.
Was she happy
you gave her the job?
Oh, my-my new assistant
was very happy
that I hired my new assistant.
( phone ringing )
Hello.
Oh, hey.
Can you, uh, can you
hang on a second?
It's the producers
over at Mac and Cheese.
If you'll excuse me
for a minute.
Hey, funny
you should call.
I was just looking over
next week's script.
Canceled?!
Like they're taking it
off the air?
Joey:
Oh.
All right.
I'll see you Monday.
We're not even shooting
them anymore?!
Well, all right.
Bye.
They canceled
Mac and Cheese!
I'm sorry.
Oh, Joey,
sorry, Joey.
Why would they do that?
That was a good show, right?
You want to tell secrets?
Okay, okay.
In college,
Ross used to wear leg warmers.
( laughs )
All right. All right.
Chandler entered a Vanilla Ice
look-alike contest and won.
Ross came in fourth and cried!
( laughing ):
Oh, my God!
Oh, is that funny?
Oh, you-you find that funny?
Well, maybe Chandler should know
some of your secrets, too.
( laughing ):
I... I already told him
everything.
You shush!
Once, Monica was sent
to her room without dinner
so she ate the macaroni
off a jewelry box she'd made.
Aah!
Um...
Ross used to stay home
every Saturday night
to watch Golden Girls.
Monica couldn't tell time
until she was 13.
It's hard for some people.
Of course it is.
Chandler one time wore
my underwear to work!
Hey!
I'm sorry I couldn't think
of any more for Ross.
Ross:
Oh, oh!
In college, Chandler got drunk
and slept with the lady
who cleaned our dorm.
( laughs )
That was you.
( Monica laughs )
Whatever, dude,
you kissed a guy.
How could this happen to me?
Yesterday I had two TV shows.
Today I've got nothing.
Well, wait a minute.
What happened
to Days of Our Lives?
Uh, well, they might be
a little mad at me over there.
Wh-wh-what happened?
Well, maybe I got
a little upset
and maybe I told them
where they could go.
Joey, why would you do that?
Because they wanted me
to audition.
You?! An actor?!
That's madness!
Rachel Green's office.
Tag?
Hi. Who was that?
Nobody.
I was just practicing.
Really?
( tittering )
Hi.
Hi. Rachel
Green's office.
You must be Hilda.
Yeah, this is Tag.
Tag, this is Phoebe.
Phoebe, could I see you
for a second?
Phoebe...
Mm-hmm.
That's a great name.
Oh, you like that?
You should hear my phone number.
Okay. We'll
be right back.
Mmm...
So, you hired yourself
a little treat, did ya?
All right, I know.
I know how it
looks, Pheebs, but
I'm telling you...
But-but you know you cannot get
involved with your assistant.
Yes, I know that.
I know that.
And I know
that hiring him
was probably not the smartest
thing that I've ever done
but I'm telling you,
from this moment on
I swear,
this is strictly professional.
( knock on door )
Yes?
Rachel:
Hi.
Hey Rachel.
Cute assistant.
What's his story?
Is he...?
Gay? Yeah.
( knock on door )
Hey...
Terry.
Joey Tribbiani!
Surprised your big head could
fit through our small halls.
I got to go, Joey.
Wait, Terry,
look, wait, uh...
I'm really sorry
about before.
I was an idiot, thinking I'm
too big to audition for you.
You got to give me
another chance.
I can't help
you, Joey.
Wait, Terry, please!
Look...
I just lost my other job, okay?
You have no idea
how much I need this.
Please, help me out.
For old times' sake.
This poor guy's
been in a coma
for five years.
It's hopeless.
It's not hopeless.
Dr. Stryker Ramoray's
a miracle worker.
Look, here he comes.
Good morning.
Drake, it's your
brother, Stryker.
Can you hear me?
Director:
And... cut!
I'm back, baby! Ha, ha, ha!
You know, in my defense, um...
there was no glitter on the
macaroni and very little glue.
And in my defense,
the cleaning lady came on to me.
You have no trouble
telling time now, right?
No.
Quick,
what time is it?
I don't know.
Time to kiss a guy, maybe?
( chuckling )
What are you laughing at,
Pampers?
You know, when I said that
because we're getting married
we should share everything
and not have any secrets?
Yeah.
Yeah, that was stupid.
Let's not do that.
Oh. Absolutely.
And we should keep all the stuff
we told each other secret
from everybody else.
Yeah, definitely.
( chuckling )
Okay, if you'll excuse me
I'm going to go hang out
with some people who don't know
the Space Mountain story.
Then I'd steer
clear of Phoebe.
Man!
Well.
Yeah, not that you would
but I wouldn't go hang out
with all the guys at my office.
( knock at door )
Hi.
Do you have a minute?
Oh, yeah, sure. What's up?
I got asked out twice today
while I was at lunch...
by guys.
Really?
Yeah.
Did you tell someone
that I was gay?
Oh, did you not want people
to know that?
No, I'm not gay.
And I especially wouldn't
want you to think I was gay.
Why's that?
I don't think I should say.
Oh, you can say.
Come on.
I don't want you to feel like
you can't tell me things.
Okay.
'kay.
Well?
Yeah.
I'd love to ask out
your friend Phoebe.
Yeah, she's gay.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]